Manzanar War Relocation Center records, 1942-1946
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Manzanar Relocation Center - War Relocation Authority photographs
  - War Relocation Authority photographs. Midland Savings Building, Denver, Colorado., ca. 90 photographs.; Mainly of Japanese who were at Manzanar, showing their activities and life after leaving the Relocation Center. Includes 60 8"×10" glossy photographs. Some of these duplicate the larger mounte
    - Top of radio in Yonometsu residence; Robert Yonometsu issoldier pictured., 36-; 62
    - Mrs. Dennis Shimizu., 37-; 101
    - Michael Yonemitsu., 38-; 17
    - Michael Yonemitsu & Harry Sumida., 39-; 16
    - Toyo Miyatake (head)., 40-; 104
    - Pvt. Kato., 41-; 12
    - Beri Katsum Miura., 42-; 73
    - C.T. Hibino, artist., 43-; 113
    - Kazuo Kageyama., 44-; 24
    - Hidemi Takenaka, woodworker., 45-; 29
    - Richard Kobayashi, cabbages., 46-; 33-A
    - Frank Nobuo Hirozawa., 47-; 27
    - Nobutero Hardy Sumida., 48-; 49
    - Henry Hanawa., 49-; 35
    - Yuichi Hitata., 50-; 47
- Manzanar Relocation Center - Ansel Adams photographs
  - Numbered and mounted photographs by Ansel Adams of Manzanar Relocation Center., Display proofs; ca. 170 photographs on 14" × 18" mats. (Box 69-72, 109)
    - Nos. 1 - 72. (Box 69)
    - Nos. 74 - 182. (Box 70)
    - Nos. 1 - 72. (Box 71)
    - Nos. 26 - 50. (Box 72)
  - Open field with mountains in background and low clouds. Photo number: 1. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Men gathered around a fire. Photo number: 2. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - View of Manzanar with only a few people outside. Photo number: 3. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - View of Manzanar with many people walking around. Photo number: 4. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Fumiko Hirata and Mr. Matsumoto sitting at a desk looking over a paper. Photo number: 4. (Box 109, Folder 30)
  - Driver unloading car. Photo number: 5. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Yuri Uyano in doorway beneath "Relocation" sign. Photo number: 5. (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Men taking care of pigs. Photo number: 6. (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Man feeding chickens. Photo number: 7. (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Close-up of part of job relocation bulletin board. Photo number: 7. (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Two men up on telephone pole. Photo number: 8. (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Philip Hara standing in front of job bulletin board. Photo number: 8. (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Close-up of Fumiko Hirata. Photo number: 9. (Box 109, Folder 29)
  - Job bulletin board. Photo number: 10. (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Close-up of Roy M. Takano's desk. Photo number: 11. (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Women looking in at a newborn baby in the hospital. Photo number: 12. (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Dressmakers gathered around table looking at dress designs. Photo number: 13. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Four women sitting on couch at a Y.W.C.A. Photo number: 13. (Box 109, Folder 28)
  - Woman working on a mannequin with dressmaking class in background. Photo number: 14. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Tom Kano in a wheelchair with his nurse, Aiko Hamaguchi. Photo number: 14. (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - General store. Photo number: 15. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Nurse Akio Hamaguchi helping her patient, Toyoki Ioki, who is lying in bed. Photo number: 15. (Box 109, Folder 27)
  - Jive Bombers band performing. Photo number: 16. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Man standing in warehouse filled with squash. Photo number: 17. (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Man and woman standing in doorway of cabin. Photo number: 18. (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Father reading newspaper at home with daugher and son listening to Beethoven. Photo number: 19. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Close-up of Nurse Aiko Hamaguchi. Photo number: 19. (Box 109, Folder 45)
  - Father playing with daughter's pigtail while rest of family watches. Photo number: 20. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Nurse Akio Hamaguchi and his friends playing bridge in the nurse's quarters. Photo number: 20. (Box 109, Folder 46)
  - Men listening to someone speak at Town Hall meeting. Photo number: 21. (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Close-up of Catherine Natsuko Yamaguchi, Red Cross nurse. Photo number: 21. (Box 109, Folder 44)
  - Mother holding child and father sitting with son on couch in their home. Photo number: 22. (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - 2 men smoking amongst cartons of soda drinks. Photo number: 23. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - George Nakano talking to Keiko Kamahara and Fumiko Tashima with Tom Kanoand Nurse Aiko Hamaguchi in the background. Photo number: 23. (Box 109, Folder 43)
  - Man and woman performing in a play. Photo number: 24. (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Woman in foreground and man in background at his desk with an adding machine. Photo number: 25. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Kazuo Kageyama working on his model boats. Photo number: 25. (Box 109, Folder 42)
  - Close-up of a policeman. Photo number: 26. (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Frank Hirozawa testing a large container of solution while his teenage assistant looks on. Photo number: 26. (Box 109, Folder 48)
  - Young man with glasses and leather jacket in front of Manzanar Christian Church services schedule. Photo number: 27. (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Women with glasses wearing a uniform and holding gloves in right hand. Photo number: 28. (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Frank Hirosama working in a laboratory. Photo number: 28. (Box 109, Folder 41)
  - Two older men reading documents, younger man smiling, large American flag in background. Photo number: 29. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Close-up of middle-aged man wearing glass, a cap, and collared shirt undersweatshirt. Photo number: 30. (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Close-up of young man wearing cap and jean jacket. Photo number: 31. (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Close-up of Benji Iguchi. Photo number: 31. (Box 109, Folder 31)
  - Close-up of a man wearing a hat and a cigarette in his mouth. Photo number: 32. (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Close-up of young woman in nurse cadet uniform wearing glasses. Photo number: 33. (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Tractor in field. Photo number: 33. (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Close-up of clean-shaven young man in military uniform. Photo number: 34. (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Close-up of Richard Kobayashi, farmer. Photo number: 34. (Box 109, Folder 26)
  - Extreme close-up of military medal on chest. Photo number: 35. (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Close-up of Henry Hanawa wearing a collared shirt. Photo number: 35. (Box 109, Folder 49)
  - Benji Iguchi and Henry Hawana - tractor repair in field. Photo number: 36. (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Close-up smiling young lady with wavy hair, white short-sleeved blouse, andpatterned skirt crocheting lace. Photo number: 37. (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Close-up of a man wearing a white shirt and a sports coat. Photo number: 37. (Box 109, Folder 25)
  - Close-up of doctor wearing glasses and scrubs leaning against a metal columnruler. Photo number: 38. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Chemistry class. Photo number: 38. (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Doctor with glasses and scrubs arranging old man's right hand for an X-ray. Photo number: 39. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Close-up of Masao Nakazawa. Photo number: 39. (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Close-up of old man with glasses and beret. Photo number: 40. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Women playing volleyball. Photo number: 40. (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Close-up of army private wearing a cap, a shirt, and a tie. Photo number: 41. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Women playing volleyball. Photo number: 41. (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Close-up of young man wearing a sweater. Photo number: 42. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Jane Harada holding a volleyball. Photo number: 42. (Box 109, Folder 39)
  - Old man with palette in hand posing in front of a landscape mural. Photo number: 43. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Woman putting up an "Education Week" Poster. Photo number: 43. (Box 109, Folder 40)
  - Close-up of middle-aged man in tweed suit. Photo number: 44. (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Close-up of Mrs. Yaeko Nakamura. Photo number: 44. (Box 109, Folder 47)
  - Close-up of young man wearing a dark cap. Photo number: 45. (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Mrs. Nakamura leading a calisthenics class. Photo number: 45. (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Boy holding cabbages. Photo number: 46. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Calisthenics class. Photo number: 46. (Box 109, Folder 35)
  - Close-up of man with glasses and mustache, Frank Hirozawa. Photo number: 47. (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Old man with glasses wearing bathrobe sitting in chair and reading a book. Photo number: 48. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Close-up of a young man wearing a denim jacket. Photo number: 49. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Extreme close-up of Yuichi Hitata. Photo number: 50. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Close-up of Eiko Yamamoto. Photo number: 50. (Box 109, Folder 36)
  - Close-up of Emiko Motooka. Photo number: 51. (Box 109, Folder 37)
  - Close-up of Louise Tamiko Nakamura. Photo number: 52. (Box 109, Folder 38)
  - Mrs. Yaeko Nakamura and her daughters, Joyce Yuki and Louise Tami. Photo number: 53. (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Close-up of Joyce Yukiko Nakamura, young girl. Photo number: 54. (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. Nakamura and family in Pleasure Park. Photo number: 55. (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Jane Harada holding a volleyball. Photo number: 56. (Box 109, Folder 33)
  - Profile of Jane Yaeko Harada. Photo number: 57. (Box 109, Folder 32)
  - Close-up of Katzumi Roy Yoshimura. Photo number: 58. (Box 109, Folder 50)
  - Close-up of Mrs. May Kikuko Ichida. Photo number: 59. (Box 109, Folder 34)
  - Two young girls in Sunday school class. Photo number: 60. (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Yuichi and Eumiko Hirata on steps of Y.M.C.A. building. Photo number: 61. (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Group standing outside of a catholic church with a priest and two nuns. Photo number: 64. (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Noboru Yamasaki and Tsugio Imamoto singing in choir. Photo number: 65. (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Louis Frizzel leading choir students who are seated. Photo number: 66. (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Akio Matsumoto making an "entrance" sign. Photo number: 67. (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Sumiko Shigematsu using a thread power machine. Photo number: 68. (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Women working in garment production. Photo number: 69. (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Bert K. Miura making patterns for clothing. Photo number: 71. (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Bert K. Miura and Toshiko Kadonada in clothes-making shop. Photo number: 72. (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Mrs. Ryie Yoshizawa holding a dress-making class. Photo number: 74. (Box 70, Folder 51)
  - Mrs. Nakamura in co-op store with daughters shopping for clothes. Photo number: 76. (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Welder working in center machine shop. Photo number: 77. (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Hidemi Tayenaka in wood-working shop. Photo number: 79. (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Hands of mechanic at lathe. Photo number: 80. (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Close-up of Bunkichi Hayashi, middle-aged man. Photo number: 81. (Box 70, Folder 48)
  - Bunkichi Hayashi, J. Benson Saks, and Chokicki Nakana sitting at desk. Photo number: 82. (Box 70, Folder 49)
  - Town Hall meeting, Roy M. Takeno standing. Photo number: 86. (Box 70, Folder 50)
  - Roy Takeno and staff in his office. Photo number: 87. (Box 70, Folder 41)
  - Three men working in warehouse. Photo number: 89. (Box 70, Folder 58)
  - Benji Iguchi and Henry Hanawa repairing a tractor. Photo number: 90. (Box 70, Folder 42)
  - Close-up of Yuri Yamzaki, high school student. Photo number: 97. (Box 70, Folder 43)
  - Close-up of Yuri Yamazaki, high school student. Photo number: 98. (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Close-up of Kay Fukuda, cadet nurse. Photo number: 100. (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Dennis Shimizu reading "Burma Surgeon" and smoking a pipe. Photo number: 102. (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Close-up of Yemiko Sedohara, secretary. Photo number: 107. (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Close-up of Michiko Sugawara, a stenographer. Photo number: 108. (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Close-up of Tetsuko Murakami, secretary. Photo number: 109. (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Close-up of Jean Namba, secretary. Photo number: 110. (Box 70, Folder 55)
  - Close-up of Kishio Matoba, a journalist, wearing a coat and a ski cap. Photo number: 111. (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - C. T. Hibino, artist (mounted with #142). Photo number: 114. (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Man feeding chickens in chicken coop. Photo number: 117. (Box 70, Folder 47)
  - Chicken farm. Photo number: 118. (Box 70, Folder 46)
  - Men pitching hay (mounted with #120). Photo number: 119. (Box 70, Folder 52)
  - Cattle grazing in a field (mounted with #119). Photo number: 120. (Box 70, Folder 52)
  - Front view of saxophone players in the Jive Bombers. Photo number: 122. (Box 70, Folder 53)
  - Little girl hiding behind the Jive Bombers music stand and a bass player inbackground (mounted with #124). Photo number: 123. (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Saxophone players of the Jive Bombers (mounted with #123). Photo number: 124. (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Joe Sakai, bass player of the Jive Bombers (mounted with #126). Photo number: 125. (Box 70, Folder 54)
  - Drummer of Jive Bombers (mounted with #125). Photo number: 126. (Box 70, Folder 54)
  - View of Manzanar from across a field on a winter day (mounted with #128). Photo number: 127. (Box 70, Folder 56)
  - View of Manzanar from across a field on a winter day (mounted with #127). Photo number: 128. (Box 70, Folder 56)
  - Manzanar in the winter. Photo number: 129. (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - View of Manzanar streets on a winter day (mounted with #131). Photo number: 130. (Box 70, Folder 57)
  - View of Manzanar streets on a winter day (mounted with #130). Photo number: 131. (Box 70, Folder 57)
  - Manzanar streets on a winter day. Photo number: 132. (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - People leaving Buddhist Service on a winter day. Photo number: 133. (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - People leaving Buddhist temple on a winter day (mounted with #135). Photo number: 134. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Buddhist service (mounted with #134). Photo number: 135. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Long line of people waiting to go into mess hall. Photo number: 136. (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - People waiting in line to go to mess hall (mounted with #138). Photo number: 137. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Interior of mess hall (mounted with #137). Photo number: 138. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Two boys eating. Photo number: 139. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - J. S. Yonai working in a butcher shop. Photo number: 140. (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - George Ogowa and J. S. Yonai working in a butcher shop. Photo number: 141. (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Men loading produce truck (mounted with #114). Photo number: 142. (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Woodrow Wakatsuki in co-op store. Photo number: 144. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Two clerks in the co-op store with pies on the counter. Photo number: 146. (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Clerk helping a customer choose thread. Photo number: 147. (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Three female students in biology class. Photo number: 149. (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Biology class at Manzanar High School (mounted with #151). Photo number: 150. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - General library at Manzanar High School (mounted with #150). Photo number: 151. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Yoshiko Joan Mori, secretary of the education department, sitting at her desk. Photo number: 152. (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Two little boys at Children's Garden. Photo number: 153. (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Mrs. Misu Naki with her baby. Photo number: 154. (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Bruce Tsurutani, a toddler, standing in doorway. Photo number: 155. (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Mrs. Otsuna Nakaji standing by open door of car looking in. Photo number: 156. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - People standing by car (mounted with #15). Photo number: 157. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - People saying goodbye to passengers in car (mounted with #157). Photo number: 158. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Driver packing van with people waiting in front of the Police Dept. (mounted with #160). Photo number: 159. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Driver packing van with people standing around (mounted with #159). Photo number: 160. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - People walking to bus with luggage. Photo number: 162. (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Group of actors acting out a scene in a play (mounted with #165). Photo number: 164. (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Backstage of high school play (mounted with #164). Photo number: 165. (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Kazuko Nagi resting her hand on Arnold Maeda's shoulder in a high school play(mounted with #167). Photo number: 166. (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Tak Ando in a high school play (mounted with #166). Photo number: 167. (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Three girls standing outside a cabin. Photo number: 168. (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Miyatake family in daughter's bedroom watching her draw. Photo number: 170. (Box 70, Folder 44)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Isurutani with son Bruce sitting at a table in their home. Photo number: 171. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Mother looking at woman standing while sitting on cot with baby on lap and daughters on cot next to her. Photo number: 179. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - People working at their desks in the Manzanar Cooperative Enterprise Office. Photo number: 182. (Box 70, Folder 45)
- War Relocation Authority (WRA) - Printed materials and reports, 1942-1946
  Printed bulletins, releases, monographs, and reports, including quarterly and semi-annual reports of the War Relocation Authority, 1942-1946.
  - WRA - Daily News Digest. Washington, D.C., November 1944 - July, 1945 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Administrative highlights of WRA program. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Community government in War Relocation Centers. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Impounded people: Japanese-Americans in the relocation centers. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Legal and constitutional phases of the WRA program. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Relocation of Japanese-Americans. The Relocation Program., May 1943. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - The wartime handling of evacuee property. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Wartime exile: The exclusion of the Japanese-Americans from the West Coast. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - WRA Quarterly reports, March - June, July-September, & October - December 1942 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - WRA Semi-annual reports, January - June & July - December 1943 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - WRA Semi-annual reports, January - June & July - December 1944 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Annual report of the director of the War Relocation Authority, (for year ending June 30, 1944) (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - WRA Semi-annual reports, January - June, July - December 1945; January - June, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - WRA releases, statements, etc., Note: Most of this material is duplicated elsewhere in the collection. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - WRA publications, Note: This material is duplicated elsewhere in the collection. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - WRA - Community analysis section. Bibliography on the Japanese in America. Part III. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - WRA - Community analysis section. Community Analyst Letter, (#1-5 & 7-13), April 1943 - February 1945. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - WRA - Community analysis section. Community Analysis Notes. (#8-12), March - April, 1945. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - WRA - Community analysis section. Trends In The Relocation Centers., November 1944 - 1945 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Manzanar Relocation Center - printed materials
  Printed publications, bulletins, reports, newspapers, etc. from the Manzanar Relocation Center.
  - Manzanar publications (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Activities Program. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - A Barrack Becomes a Home, 2 copies. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Classes for the Physically Handicapped. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Manzanar Libraries (and Visual Aid Program). (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Toy Loan Library. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Family Security in America: Where Shall I Find It?. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Reinstitution of Selective Service, June 1944. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous publications re: Manzanar. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Manzanar Cooperative Enterprises, Inc. Balance sheets, February, September, November, December 1944 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Manzanar - school related materials (forms, etc.). (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Manzanar school publications. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Our World, Manzanar High annual, 1943-1944. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Our world, 1943-1944, Manzanar High (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - *Campus Pepper. Manzanar high school newspaper. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - *Manzanar Whirlwind. Manzanar elementary school paper. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - *Manzanar Free Press (scattered issues). (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - *Manzanar Relocation Supplement, April 21-Aug. 29, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Manzanar church publications - Manzanar Buddhist church and Manzanar Christian church. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - *Manzanar Adult Education Quarterly Report - Summer Semester, *Originals are in Box 108 (not available for use, due to fragile condition.) Acid-free copies, in Box 59, are available for consultation. (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Relocation center newspapers
  Printed publications of Manzanar and other relocation centers. Includes Poston, Arizona; Rivers, Arizona; Rohwer, Arkansas; Denson, Arkansas; Newell, California; Amache, Colorado; Hunt, Idaho; Topaz, Utah; Heart Mountain, Wyoming. Also includes Santa Anita, Tulare and Tanforan, California assembly centers.
  - Gila River, Arizona
    - Gila News Courier., September 1942-August 1943; 1 bound volume. (Box 84)
    - Gila News Courier., August 1943-January 1944; 1 bound volume. (Box 75)
    - Gila News Courier., February-December 1944; 1 bound volume. (Box 75)
    - Gila News Courier., July 1944-June 1945; 1 bound volume. (Box 76)
    - Gila News Courier, vol. 3, nos. 135-174., July-September 1944; [duplicated in bound volume in Box 76.] (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous Gila publications, 1 bound volume: (Box 79)
      - Gila Bulletin., September 8-November 9, 1945 (Box 79)
        A copy of this item is in the Negative Microfilm Collection #04576.
      - Gila Co-op News., June 17-October 5, 1943 (Box 79)
      - Gila News Courier., January 3-September 5, 1945 (Box 79)
  - Poston, Arizona
    - Poston Chronicle., December 1942-April 1943; 1 bound volume. (Box 85)
    - Poston Chronicle., April-December 1943; 1 bound volume. (Box 86)
    - Poston Chronicle., December 1943-June 1944; 1 bound volume. (Box 102)
    - Poston Chronicle., July-December 1944; 1 bound volume. (Box 87)
    - Poston Information Bulletin., April-October 1942; 1 bound volume. (Box 103)
    - Poston Information Bulletin., October 1942-December 1943; 1 bound volume. (Box 88)
  - Denson, Arkansas
    - Denson Communique., October 1942-February 1943; 1 bound volume.; A copy of this item is in the Negative Microfilm Collection #04566. (Box 89)
    - Denson Tribune., March-September 1943; 1 bound volume. (Box 89)
    - Denson Tribune., April-September 1943; [duplicated in bound volume in Box 89.] (Box 60)
    - Denson Tribune., September 1943-June 1944; 1 bound volume. (Box 87)
  - Rohwer, Arkansas
    - Rohwer Jiho., January 1944-November 1945; 1 bound volume. (Box 93-95)
    - Rohwer Outpost., October 1942-August 1945; 3 bound volumes.; The following issues are on negative microfilm #06599: October 24, 1942-February 6, 1943 February 13-24, 1943 June 3, 7 & 17, 1944 (Box 96)
    - Miscellaneous Rohwer publications., 2 bound volumes: (Box 96-97)
      Clearwater Clarion Call, 1942-1944.
      The Daybreak, 1944.
      Federated Christian Church Bulletin, 1943.
      Hi-lites, 1943-1944.
      Roar, 1944.
      Rohwer Relocater, 1945.
      Sangha News, 1944.
      Summer Breeze, 1944.
      Transmitter, 1943.
  - Arcadia, California
    - Santa Anita Pacemaker., April-October 1942; 1 bound volume. (Box 102)
    - Santa Anita Pacemaker., Duplicate file from L.A. Harbor College, 10/23/68 (unbound). (Box 103)
  - Manzanar, California
    - Manzanar Free Press., April 1942-October 1945; MICROFILM 04388; Digitized microfilm.; Entire run of the publication.
      - July 1942
        - Manzanar free press, July 22, 1942, 1942-07-22
        - Manzanar free press, July 24, 1942, 1942-07-24
        - Manzanar free press, July 27, 1942, 1942-07-27